Guide to the Margaret Flory Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- World's Student Christian Federation, Series VII
  - Assemblies, Conferences, Meetings and Seminars
    - Miscellaneous Meetings and Conferences
      - Preparatory Material for Consultation Celigny, Switzerland, 1965 (Box 121, Folder 1366)
      - Regional Meetings: Washington D.C., 1994 (Box 111, Folder 1263)
      - World Conference of Christian Youth, 1947 (Box 52, Folder 391)
  - Projects and Programs
    - WSCF Centennial (1895-1995)
      - General (Box 52, Folder 392)
      - General, 1995 (Box 121, Folder 1367)
      - WSCF Bibliography, 1995 (Box 121, Folder 1368)
      - Posters (Box 111, Folder 1264)
      - History and Archives Project -- International, 1990-1995 (Box 52, Folder 393)
      - History and Archives Project -- Geneva Meeting, Feb. 22-27, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 394)
      - History and Archives Project -- U.S. Working Group, 1992-1995 (Box 52, Folder 395)
      - History and Archives Project -- Collected Essays (Box 52, Folder 396)
      - History and Archives Project -- Potter Consultation, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 397-398)
      - History and Archives Project -- Working Papers: "The Christian Presence in U.S. Universities/Colleges, 1960-1994" (Box 111, Folder 1265)
      - History and Archives Project -- ISF: International Study Fellowship, 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1266)
      - Centennial Fund -- International, 1989-1995 (Box 52, Folder 399)
      - Centennial Fund -- USA, 1992-1995 (Box 52, Folder 400)
      - Centennial: Senior Friends Directory, 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1267)
      - U.S. Programs, 1989-1995 (Box 53, Folder 401)
      - U.S. Regional Meetings, 1992-1995 (Box 53, Folder 402)
      - Senior Friends Meeting, Berlin, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 403-404)
    - Life and Mission of the Church (LMC) Emphasis
      - Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 53, Folder 405-406)
      - Miscellaneous Publications, 1959-1963 (Box 111, Folder 1268)
      - Program Planning (Box 53, Folder 407)
      - LMC Bulletin No. 1-2, 4, and 7 (Newsletter), 1958-1959 (Box 121, Folder 1369)
      - LMC Conference, Maryland, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 408)
      - LMC Conference, Maryland, Memos and Program Planning, 1956-1957 (Box 121, Folder 1370)
      - LMC Consultation, New York (PCUSA Board of Foreign Missions): Christian Students and the Mission of the Church, 1957 (Box 111, Folder 1269)
      - LMC Conference, Georgia, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 409)
      - LMC Conference, Radnor, Penn. (Presbyterian Students): Responsibility of the Laity for the Mission of the Church, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 410)
      - Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 121, Folder 1371)
      - General, n.d. (Box 121, Folder 1272)
      - Program Planning, 1956-1959 (Box 121, Folder 1273)
      - LMC Conference, Mexico City, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 411)
      - LMC Conference, Middle East, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 412)
      - Strasbourg Teaching Conference, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 413-417)
      - Strasbourg Teaching Conference, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 418-424)
      - Strasbourg Teaching Conference: "The Student World" - 2 issues on conference, 1961 (Box 112, Folder 1270)
      - Strasbourg Teaching Conference: Study Series - "The Life and Mission of the Church", 1958 (Box 112, Folder 1271)
      - Strasbourg Teaching Conference: Summary Document, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 425)
      - Strasbourg Teaching Conference: Travel, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 426)
      - Strasbourg Teaching Conference: Trip to Prague, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 427)
    - Miscellaneous Projects and Programs
      - Ecumenical Assistance Program, 1959-1963 (Box 54, Folder 428-429)
      - Ecumenical Solidarity Fund, 1983-1987 (Box 55, Folder 430)
      - Ecumenical Strategy in the Academic World -- General, 1963-1968 (Box 55, Folder 431)
      - Ecumenical Approach to Christian Presence in Universities Abroad -- United Presbyterian Consultation, Krisheim House, Philadelphia, 1965 (Box 112, Folder 1272)
      - Ecumenical Strategy -- Latin America Consultation, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 432)
      - Ecumenical Strategy -- Africa Consultation, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 433)
      - Ecumenical Strategy -- Asia Consultation, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 434-435)
      - International Study Fellowship, 1962-1965 (Box 55, Folder 436-438)
      - Joint Experimental Program (with Pax Romana), 1972 (Box 55, Folder 438a)
      - Missing Senior Friends, 1984-1988 (Box 112, Folder 1273)
      - Philippe Maury Memorial Living Event, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 439)
      - 2nd Century Fund: Printed Material, 2002 (Box 112, Folder 1274)
      - Senior Friends List, 1990 (Box 112, Folder 1275)
      - Survey: U.S. Boards of Missions Involvement in Student Work, 1954 (Box 56, Folder 440-443)
      - Universal Day of Prayer, 1954-1995 (Box 56, Folder 444)
      - Universal Day of Prayer, 1963 (Box 121, Folder 1274)
      - United Institute of Technology (Box 56, Folder 445)
      - Visitation Team, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 446)
  - Correspondence
    - Agitprop, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 447)
    - Correspondence with and re: D.T. Niles, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 1274a)
    - Galland, Valdo, 1958-1963 (Box 56, Folder 448)
    - Ilano, Josefa A. (Box 112, Folder 1276)
    - Johnson, Peter (Box 56, Folder 449)
    - Jordan, Carino, and Fritschel, 1966, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 450)
    - Lehtonen, Risto, 1971-1972 (Box 112, Folder 1277)
    - Regarding: Hunting for Addresses, 1969, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 451)
    - Regarding: "Open Letter", 1977 (Box 56, Folder 452)
    - Regional Offices (Box 56, Folder 453)
    - Wilson, Donald (Box 56, Folder 454)
    - General, 1950-1990 (Box 57, Folder 454a-462)
    - Regarding 1996: Resignations (Box 112, Folder 1279)
    - Regarding the book "From Past to Future: Experiments in Global Bridging", 1997 (Box 112, Folder 1284)
    - Regarding fund drive for new Headquarters, 1968-1970 (Box 112, Folder 1285)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Financial Documents, 1961-1977 (Box 57, Folder 463)
    - Introduction Form, 1962 (Box 57, Folder 464)
    - Geneva Trip, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 465)
    - Photographs: Carino, Mitri, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 465a)
    - Photographs: Broumana Conference, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 465b)
    - Prayer Calendar, 1961-1962 (Box 57, Folder 465c)
    - Publication Lists (Box 57, Folder 466)
    - National SCMs (Box 57, Folder 467)
    - Who We Are (Box 57, Folder 468)
    - Flory Reflections on 37 years in the Federation, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 1280)
    - Essay: "Experiences and Perspectives Drawn from the renewal of the Churches in the West" by Hans-Ruedi Weber (Box 112, Folder 1281)
    - Essay on Changing Christian Perspective in the University - Anon., n.d. (Box 112, Folder 1282)
    - Photos of Flory with Federation, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 1283)
    - 75th Anniversary, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 1286)
    - Speech at Princeton (International Study Fellowship meeting?), n.d. (Box 112, Folder 1287)
    - Directory, 1964-1965 (Box 112, Folder 1288)
    - "In Memoriam: Philippe Maury 1916-1967" (Box 121, Folder 1275)
    - WSCF Credentials for Margaret Flory, 1952 (Box 121, Folder 1276)
    - General, 1962, 1967, n.d. (Box 121, Folder 1277)
    - "Three Years' Report: Chapter VIII on the Frontiers of the Church (Missions)", n.d. (Box 121, Folder 1278)
    - Women in the WSCF, 1989-1998 (Box 121, Folder 1279)
  - Printed Material
    - Centennial Brochure, 1995 (Box 113, Folder 1289)
    - "The Federation Cross", 1949 (Box 113, Folder 1290)
    - "Federation News" - December No. 1, 2001 (Box 113, Folder 1291)
    - "New World Outlook" by Kenneth Guest, 1996 (Box 113, Folder 1292)
    - "The Role of Students in the Missionary Movement" by Emidio Campi, 1988? (Box 113, Folder 1292a)
    - "The 2008 Annual Report of the World Student Christian Federation" (Box 121, Folder 1280)
    - "The Bank and Apartheid: an Open Letter from WSCF" (Box 121, Folder 1281)
    - "Federation News" - Jan/Feb, 1958 (Box 121, Folder 1282)
    - "Friends of the WSCF" (Newsletter), 2002 (Box 121, Folder 1283)
    - "The Middle Generation", 1969 (Box 121, Folder 1284)
    - "WSCF 34th General Assembly: Report of the Senior Friends Gathering", 2008 (Box 121, Folder 1285)
    - "WSCF Europe" -February No. 27, 1982 (Box 121, Folder 1286)
    - "WSCF Journal: a Quarterly" -August V. IV No. 213, 1983 (Box 121, Folder 1287)
- National and World Councils of Churches, Series VIII
  - National Council of Churches (NCC) Committee on Cooperation in Latin America (CCLA) Committee on Youth and Student Work
    - General, 1953-1990s (Box 58, Folder 469-473a)
  - NCC Division of Overseas Ministries
    - "Prophecy in a Technocratic Era," Address to First Assembly, Arend Theodoor van Leeuwen, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 474)
    - Education Committee, 1965, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 475-476)
    - Education Committee, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 476)
    - Education Committee: Report of Joint Study Commission on Education (WCC/World Council of Christian Education), 1967 (Box 58, Folder 477)
    - Education Committee, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 478)
    - Europe Committee, Ireland Program, 1976, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 478a)
    - Africa Emphasis, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 479)
    - Friends From Abroad Directories, Leadership Development Committee, 1980, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 480)
  - NCC Commission on Higher Education (Department of Higher Education after 1965)
    - General, 1956-1958 (Box 59, Folder 481)
    - Administrative Committee, 1959 (Box 59, Folder 482)
    - General, 1962 (Box 59, Folder 483)
    - Theological Education Fund, 1963 (Box 59, Folder 484)
    - The Churches and Higher Education: Background Papers, 1963 (Box 59, Folder 485)
    - Committee of National Staff, 1963 (Box 59, Folder 486)
    - "The Christian Mission and Higher Education," Address by Daniel Day Williams, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 487)
    - Committee of National Staff, 1966, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 488-489)
    - Colloquium on New Directions in Higher Education, 1967-1968 (Box 59, Folder 490)
    - Internationalization in Higher Education and the Church's Ministry, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 491)
  - NCC Miscellaneous
    - "The Missionary Obligation of the Church" Report, 1952 (Box 59, Folder 492)
    - Institute of Overseas Churchmanship, 1962 (Box 59, Folder 492a)
    - Commission on Ecumenical Voluntary Service, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 492b)
    - National Project for the Cooperative Enlistment of the Church's Ministry, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 492c)
    - Department of International Affairs, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 493)
    - Ecumenical Exchange and Scholarship Program, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 494-495)
    - Faith and Order: Working Paper on Studies and Projects, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 496)
    - Learning and Change Workshop, Paulo Freire, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 497)
    - Governing Board Panel on Ecumenical Commitment and the NCCC Purposes, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 497a)
    - Commission on Education for Mission, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 497b)
    - Ecumenical Event (30th Anniversary), Cleveland, 5-7 Nov. 1981, Program Book (Box 60, Folder 498)
    - Ecumenical Event Correspondence and Notes, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 499)
    - Ecumenical Event Worship, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 500)
    - Future Mission and Resources, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 500a)
    - Consultation on Issues of Internationalization, New York, New York, 1974 (Box 122, Folder 1288)
  - World Council of Churches
    - International Missionary Council Integration, 1958 (Box 60, Folder 501)
    - Student Seminars (Africa, Asia), 1960 (Box 60, Folder 502)
    - Vatican Congress on "Spiritual Values of Tourism" (M. Flory, delegate), 1967 (Box 60, Folder 502a)
    - Ecumenical Youth Service, 1967 (Box 60, Folder 503)
    - Personnel List, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 503a)
    - Correspondence regarding Rev. R. N. Weinman, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 503b)
    - Ecumenical Sharing of Resources, 1972-1987 (Box 60, Folder 504-505)
    - Fifth Assembly, Message from Russian Orthodox Clergy, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 505a)
    - Commission on the Churches' Participation in Development, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 506)
    - Projects, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 507)
    - "A Conversation with Dr. Philip A. Potter," Public Affairs Program, NBC TV, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 507a)
    - Sixth Assembly, Bellingham, Washington, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 508)
    - Dr. Eugene Carson Blake, General Secretary, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 509)
    - World Conference on Mission and Evangelism, San Antonio, TX, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 509a)
    - Ecumenical Institute, Bossey, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 510)
    - General, 1980-2004 (Box 60, Folder 510a)
    - Publications (Women) (Box 60, Folder 510b)
    - Ecumenical Sharing of Resources, 1977 (Box 122, Folder 1289)
- Bi-National Service, Series IX
  - Organizational documentation
    - Annual Reports, 1975-2001 (Box 61, Folder 511-524)
    - Week of Work: Index of Meetings 1970-2000 (Box 62, Folder 524a)
    - Week of Work, Vieques, Puerto Rico, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 525-527)
    - Week of Work, Prague, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 528)
    - Week of Work, San Anselmo, CA, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 529)
    - Week of Work, Nicaragua, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 530)
    - Week of Work, Decatur, GA, 1991 (Box 62, Folder 531)
    - Week of Work, Stony Point, NY, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 532-533)
    - Week of Work, Korea, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 534)
    - Week of Work, Warren Wilson College, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 535-537)
    - Week of Work, Bossey, Switzerland, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 538)
    - Week of Work, Kirkridge, PA, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 539)
    - Week of Work, Tucson, Arizona, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 540)
    - Correspondence, Etc., 1969-1979 (Box 63, Folder 541-545)
    - Correspondence, Etc., 1980-2001 (Box 64, Folder 546-557)
    - Council, 1972-1997 (Box 104, Folder 1180-1193)
  - Printed Material
    - "Links" - Newsletters (Box 105, Folder 1194)
    - "Occasional Papers" (Box 105, Folder 1195)
    - Master Forms (Box 105, Folder 1196)
    - Fliers and Handbooks (Box 105, Folder 1197)
    - Fliers, n.d. (Box 122, Folder 1293)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Program Agency Status - Draft to 184th PCUSA General Assembly, 1972 (Box 105, Folder 1198)
    - Open Letter, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 1199)
    - "Reflections on its Development" by M. Flory, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 1200)
    - Europe Area Coordinating Group, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 1201)
    - Demilitarization/Disarmament - Collected Materials, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 1202)
    - Finances, 1979-1981 (Box 105, Folder 1203)
    - 10th Year Report, 1981 (Box 105, Folder 1204)
    - Covenant Renewal, 1982 (Box 105, Folder 1205)
    - Paper and Correspondence RE: "Partnership, Mutuality, and Incarnational Solidarity", 1988-1989 (Box 105, Folder 1206)
    - Mission Study, The Philippines, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 1207)
    - Responsible Tourism (Virginia Hadsell), 1988-1991 (Box 106, Folder 1208)
    - 20th Year Servant Update, 1991 (Box 106, Folder 1209)
    - 20th Year Anniversary, 1991 (Box 106, Folder 1210)
    - Beyond the Columbus Myth, 1992 (Box 106, Folder 1211)
    - 30th Year Celebration, 2000 (Box 106, Folder 1212)
    - Africa Conversations at Stony Point, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 1213)
    - Notebook Pages, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 1214)
    - Directories of Servants (Box 106, Folder 1215)
    - Miscellaneous Information, n.d. (Box 122, Folder 1290)
    - Margaret Flory's 1992 Annual Reflection/Report (Box 122, Folder 1291)
    - BNS 20th Anniversary, 1991 (Box 122, Folder 1292)
  - Collected Material
    - Miscellaneous Articles and Photos (Box 106, Folder 1216)
    - Servant Essays, Newsletters, and Publications (Box 106, Folder 1217)
    - Worship Materials (Box 106, Folder 1218)
- Asian Women's Institute, Series X
  - General/Collected Materials
    - Events and Proceedings Leading to the Formation of AWI, up to 1972 (Box 65, Folder 557b)
    - Establishing and Defining Writings, 1972-1975 (Box 65, Folder 557c)
    - General, 1972-1990 (Box 65, Folder 558)
    - Notes and Memoranda (Box 65, Folder 559)
    - Brochures, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 560)
    - Essays and Articles, 1960-1990 (Box 65, Folder 561-562)
    - M. Flory, "Half the Sky in China," in Asian Woman, Sept. 1977 (Box 65, Folder 563)
    - M. Flory, "Asian Women's Institute: Common Hope and Commitment" in Response: United Methodist Women, Dec. 1980 (Box 65, Folder 564)
    - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Consultation on Women in Asia, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 565)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968-1991 (Box 65, Folder 566)
    - AWI Constitution and Policy Statements, 1978, 1980 (Box 122, Folder 1294)
    - Brochures, n.d. (Box 122, Folder 1295)
    - General, 1978-1988 (Box 122, Folder 1296)
    - Newsletters, 1976-1993 (Box 122, Folder 1297)
    - Presidents' Consultation, 1981, 1985 (Box 122, Folder 1298)
  - Programs and Events
    - Ecumenical Sharing of Resources, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 567)
    - Mira Phailbus, U.S. Tour, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 568)
    - Women and Work, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 569)
    - Leadership Development, 1985-1991 (Box 65, Folder 570)
    - United Assembly Workshop, Indiana, July, 1977 (Box 103, Folder 1160)
    - AWI Conference Report, Salatiga, Indonesia, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 1299)
    - Ecumenical Sharing of Resources, 1980 (Box 122, Folder 1300)
    - Leadership Development, 1985-1988 (Box 122, Folder 1301)
    - Margaret Flory Forum, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 1302)
  - Committees/Groups
    - Committee of 75, 1975-1981 (Box 65, Folder 571)
    - Association, General (M. Flory, Chair), 1978-1989 (Box 65, Folder 572)
    - Association, Study Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 65, Folder 573)
    - Association, Report to Executive Committee, 1978-1985 (Box 65, Folder 574)
    - Executive Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 65, Folder 575)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, Stony Point, NY, 1982 (Box 103, Folder 1161)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, Seoul, Korea, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 1162)
    - Executive Committee, Joint Meetings, 1979-1986 (Box 65, Folder 576)
    - Pittsburgh Cluster, 1980-1989 (Box 66, Folder 577)
    - Support Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 66, Folder 578)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, Stony Point, NY, 1982, 1986 (Box 122, Folder 1303)
  - Financial
    - Budgets, 1980-1987 (Box 66, Folder 579)
    - Church Women United -- Grant Applications, 1979-1984 (Box 66, Folder 580)
    - Church Women United -- Financial Memoranda, 1980-1988 (Box 66, Folder 581)
    - Financial Reports, 1978-1988 (Box 123, Folder 1304)
  - Correspondence
    - General, 1967-1983 (Box 66, Folder 582-585)
    - General, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 1163)
    - General, 1985-1991 (Box 66, Folder 586-587)
    - Mailing Lists, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 588)
    - General, 1976-1988 (Box 123, Folder 1305)
  - Colleges, Centers, and Associations
    - ACWE (Association of Christians for Women's Education in Asia) (Box 103, Folder 1164)
    - Beirut College for Women (Box 103, Folder 1165)
    - Birzeit University: Israel (Box 103, Folder 1166)
    - EWHA Woman's University: Seoul, Korea (Box 103, Folder 1167)
    - Isabella Thoburn College: Lucknow, India (Box 103, Folder 1168)
    - Kinnaird College: Lahore, Pakistan (Box 103, Folder 1169)
    - Korean Women's Institute (Box 103, Folder 1170)
    - Libamba Cameroun Christian College (Box 103, Folder 1171)
    - Ludhiana Christian Medical College: Punjab, India (Box 103, Folder 1172)
    - National and World Council of Churches (Box 103, Folder 1173)
    - Saint Christopher's Training College: Vepery - Madras, India (Box 103, Folder 1174)
    - Silliman University: Dumaguete City, Philippines (Box 103, Folder 1175)
    - Tokyo Woman's Christian University: Tokyo, Japan (Box 103, Folder 1176)
    - Tunghai University: Taiwan (Box 103, Folder 1177)
    - Women's Christian College: Madras, India (Box 103, Folder 1178)
    - Miscellaneous Photos of Colleges (Box 103, Folder 1179)
    - Tokyo Woman's Christian University: Tokyo, Japan (Box 123, Folder 1306)
- United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Series XI
  - Missions: Board of Foreign Missions/Commission on Ecumenical Mission and Relations (COEMAR)/Program Agency Missions Unit
    - Internationalization of Mission
      - Fraternal Workers to the USA Program, 1952-1962 (Box 66a, Folder 588a)
      - Ad Hoc Group on Internationalization, 1966-1967 (Box 66a, Folder 588b-588c)
      - Coordinating Committee on Internationalization, 1971-1972 (Box 66a, Folder 588)
      - The Internationalization of Mission in the U.S.A.: Study Paper, 1972 (Box 66a, Folder 588e)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1979 (Box 66a, Folder 588f-588g)
      - Local/Regional Internationalization Programs, 1974-1980 (Box 66a, Folder 588h)
      - Ecumenical Ministry Project, 1974-1985 (Box 66a, Folder 588i)
      - International Student Resumes, 1979 (Box 66a, Folder 588j)
      - Mission to the U.S.A. (People in Mission program), 1978-1993 (Box 66a, Folder 588k)
      - Mission to the U.S.A., Occasional Bulletin, 1977-1981 (Box 66a, Folder 588l)
      - Global Profile Project, Photo Album, 1979 (Box 107)
      - Ad Hoc Group on Internationalization, 1966-1967 (Box 123, Folder 1307)
    - Youth Emphasis Year 1953 (M. Flory, Chair)
      - Plans/Recommendations, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 589)
      - "It Is Being Done" Report, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 590)
      - Committee Packet, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 591)
      - Projects/Budgets, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 592)
      - Regional Requests and Reports, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 593)
      - Projects Report, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 594)
      - International Fellowship Teams, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 595)
      - Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 67, Folder 596)
      - Bulletin Board Newsletter, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 597)
      - Publications, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 598)
      - Staff Conference, 6-9 Feb. 1952 (Box 67, Folder 599)
      - Furloughed Missionaries Conferences, Sept. 1952 (Box 67, Folder 600)
      - Christian Youth Conference, 1952-53, 1952-1953 (Box 67, Folder 601)
    - Office of Youth Relations
      - General
        - Youth Leader Training, 1948-1952 (Box 68, Folder 602)
        - United Christian Youth Movement, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 602a)
        - Pen-Pal Program, 1958 (Box 68, Folder 603)
        - Youth Ministry Organization Minutes, 1958-1963 (Box 68, Folder 603a)
        - "A Brief Sketch of the Development of Youth Work in the United Presbyterian Church, U.S.A.", 1960 (Box 68, Folder 603b)
        - High School Summer Program, 1964 (Box 68, Folder 604)
      - Youth Exchange Programs
        - Latin America, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 605)
        - British Isles Presbyterian Youth Exchange, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 606)
        - British Isles Presbyterian Youth Exchange, 1963 (Box 68, Folder 607)
        - International Christian Youth Exchange, 1963-1971 (Box 68, Folder 608-608a)
      - Ecumenical Youth Caravan
        - General, 1957-1962 (Box 68, Folder 609)
        - USA, 1957 (Box 68, Folder 610-611)
        - Japan, 1958 (Box 68, Folder 612)
        - Sudan, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 613)
        - USA, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 614)
        - Mexico, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 615)
        - Kenya, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 616)
    - Women's Committees
      - Women's Work Committee (Box 69, Folder 617-620)
      - Women's Advisory Committee (Box 69, Folder 621-623)
    - Board of Foreign Missions/COEMAR General Files: Events, Groups, Records, Miscellaneous
      - Ecumenical Mission Materials, 1954-1960 (Box 69, Folder 624)
      - "A New Name for the Foreign Board", 1955 (Box 69, Folder 624a)
      - Study Fellowship for New Missionaries, 1955 (Box 69, Folder 625)
      - Study Fellowship for New Missionaries, 1956-1957 (Box 69, Folder 626)
      - Office of Leadership Development: Scholarship Programs Manual (M. Flory initiative), 1956-1963 (Box 69, Folder 626a)
      - World Consultation, Lake Mohonk, NY -- Report, 1956 (Box 70, Folder 627)
      - World Consultation, Lake Mohonk, NY -- Long Range Study Material, 1956 (Box 70, Folder 628)
      - World Consultation, Lake Mohonk, NY -- General, 1956 (Box 70, Folder 629)
      - Staff Seminar -- Program Notebook, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 630)